Let's go.
I have something to tell you.
What have you done?
What on earth have you done?
What are you doing?
You took the words right out of my mouth.
Go.
Don't go.
Don't give her orders in front of me.
You have no right to order me.
Really?
Do you really think so?
Do Hoon!
Are you crazy?
Why are you doing this?
Why?
What do you want to do?
It sucks.
Do Hoon, are you okay?
How can I make you listen to me?
Jo Min Hyuk! He has known our relationship since the beginning.
What are you talking about?
He keeps on doing this even though he knew our relationship.
Impossible.
He made us to meet each other on purpose?
I told you not to see him.
Hello.
If I weren't here, you'd follow him anywhere?
What are you wearing?
I had no choice. He forced me to do it.
If he asked, would you sell yourself?
Eight of 12 votes voted in favor
of the dismissal of the CEO, Jo Min Hyuk.
You!
What are you doing?
I told you to stay with Min Hyuk.
Where were you when Min Hyuk got himself in trouble, you idiot!
I'm sorry.
Sorry can't deal with anything.
Stop it, dad!
He was doing what I told him to do.
They have approved your dismissal.
What are you talking about?
Se Yeon is the one of those who vote in favor of your dismissal.
- Get out! - Father.
Get out, you bastard!
You did this?
Yoo Jung isn't enough? So you hit Do Hoon?
You're not apologizing after what you've done?
I told you not to side with him in front of me.
Apologize?
He's the one who should apologize.
Why should I apologize?
Why?
- Jo Min Hyuk! - Why?
What are you doing? Jo Min Hyuk!
Do Hoon! Let's go!
If you want the hotel, why didn't you tell me?
I could've given it to you as a wedding present.
I don't want the hotel.
Not only did you bring another woman to a party,
you also started a fight because of her.
When can you grow up?
Do you know how embarrassed I am?
Se Yeon, President Jo might hear you.
Shut up!
Let's go.
If he remained in his position,
his career in hotel might be ended soon.
Is that why you took the lead in ousting Min Hyuk?
I know for sure that two of them support you all the times.
We can bring Min Hyuk back when we have a new board members next year.
That's none of your business.
I'll take care of it.
Look, we can't let others know that they support us.
Check out who found it out.
Yes, sir!
What happened to your mouth?
Nothing.
I don't think I paid for what I did.
I won't forget it as long as I live.
How can I forget?
I'm ashamed of
what I did to that woman.
Did you really see her and walk away?
Yes! I did it.
What do you want?
Haven't you tortured me enough?
Crazy girl. What have you done?
Kwang Soo. How can this happen?
They were at the coffee shop together.
Whether they were in the same car...
Continue your investigation.
After he proposed to her, they went home separately?
Does that make sense?
I don't think he will let it slide this time.
No matter how obnoxious he is,
we can't ignore Se Gwang's power.
He wants you to apologize in person.
Apologize to him tomorrow.
Apologize.
I'll apologize to him.
But he should apologize to the girl that he humiliated first.
Who is that girl?
Someone I care about.
You have to be careful
What's this?
You're a substandard product.
She'd do anything for money, right?
Don't prentend to be noble.
Go buy a clothes.
She'd do anything.
Only for me.
Aren't you going to tell me what happened yesterday?
Keeping your mouth shut isn't the solution.
You're smiling again. Something must've happened.
Get some rest.
You had a fever yesterday.
I need to keep this job.
Is that yours?
See you later.
Driver!
Kang Yoo Jung!
Jo Min Hyuk! He knows about our relationship.
He keeps on doing this even though he knew our relationship.
What is it now?
What do you want from me?
When are you going to stop?
When can you tell me the truth?
What are you talking about?
What are your trying to protect?
You and Ahn Do Hoon. What are you hiding?
Excuse me!
I killed someone.
It was a hit-and-run.
I hit someone and ran away.
Hey!
I said it! Are you happy?
Isn't this what you wanted?
Driver!
Isn't it enough?
You want to see me dead in front of you?
Let me go!
Pull yourself together!
Are you crazy?
Yes, I'm crazy.
Kang Yoo Jung!
Are you crazy?
Kwang Soo! Can you believe her?
She isn't even afraid of death.
What is it that she wants to protect so badly?
I'll get the car.
No.
I'm good.
I have nothing to say to you.
Tell Min Hyuk to come and apologize to me.
Jo Min Hyuk won't come.
He's going to hide behind his lawyer?
Get out.
Don't send that article to the media.
In this day and age, a company can never control the media.
Don't be so modest.
If you send it the media, then it would be a public opinion.
The even you cancelled in K Hotel
will continute to hold.
Who do you think I am?
You're the next CEO of the Segwang Corporation.
Open the envelope first.
What the heck is this?
I guess it's not enough for you
to just publish some gossip news of Jo Min Hyuk.
Hey!
Yes?
Have you ever lost an argument?
So far, no.
You'll win all your cases when you become a prosecutor.
I hope so.
Do you think you'll still help me if I'm in need?
I'll help those who have no money and no power.
What about those who have money and power?
They'll be able to take care of themselves.
What if you pretend that you don't know me?
You can show me this.
I'll help you.
As much as you hate to see me, I sufferd a lot facing you.
I don't want to see you again.
It's not your fault.
What happened to Min Hyuk isn't your fault.
You scared me sometimes.
How can you know what I was thinking about just by my expression?
Yes. I shouldn't have done that.
Have you eaten?
Why do you ask? Can't you guess?
I'm paying you to work for my hotel,
not to flirt with my fiancee.
It shouldn't concern you who I go out with.
You said I could date anyone
as long as I marry you according to the contract.
It depends on who you are dating with.
You should at leaast date with someone of equal status.
Never mind what he said. He won't mind it as well.
Se Yeon.
Where do you want to eat?
This smell might ruin your beautiful clothes.
You're the only girl that Do Hoon has brought here.
She's my colleague.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
I dried it myself.
I put the ingredients after frying them, so it should be delicious.
It looks delicious.
- Thank you. - Enjoy your meal.
Wow! You have long fingers.
So beautiful.
What do you do?
Are you a lawyer?
No. I'm a painter.
A painter.
No wonder you have a unique temperament.
Where do you live?
What does your father do?
Mother.
We're here to eat dinner.
Sorry.
I shouldn't have bothered you two.
I don't think she knows how to eat this.
I'll help her out.
It's delicious. Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Min Hyuk, start visiting our restaurant branches tomorrow.
Doing something like that might help you.
You just give me a restaurant and ask me to step aside.
You should be satisfied with that.
You bring this on yourself.
It's Ahn Do Hoon who clane up the mess for you.
Don't you feel ashamed of that?
Father!
I'm done taking care of you.
You should depend on yourself from now on.
Honey, don't you think
you should give more shares to Min Joo?
How can they kick people out just like that?
If you want to come back to the hotel next year,
improve the performance of this restaurant.
Why don't you run it for my brother?
You're way smarter than him.
Min Joo!
What?
Min Hyuk would be happy about that.
He could idle about as he wishes.
Honey! Honey!
I know my father.
I don't think he just hires people without checking.
So?
I'm sure you did a thorough background check.
Give me the all the inforamtion you got regarding Ahn Do Hoon.
Aren't you going home?
I'm waiting for Yoo Jung.
Yoo Jung!
How come you didn't come to work?
What happened?
You said you were going to work.
I told him that you were sick,
but if you miss work again...
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Hae Ri.
You've been acting weird since yesterday.
What's going on?
Tell me.
She's driving me crazy.
I guess I should've known. She won't talk.
If Yoo Jung decides not to talk, that's it.
What? Did you come with my boss' secretary?
Why don't you tell him to come in?
Yes, sir.
Are you spying on me now?
I don't like the way you're keeping an eye on me.
Do I need to disappear completely,
so you can stop harassing me?
Driver.
If what you did today happens again.
Hey, I was just worried...
Sorry, it's my fault.
I told you to make things right.
Never mind. Come home.
Bring Ahn Do Hoon here tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
You got promoted thanks to me. Shouldn't you be thanking me?
Thanks to you, I've become busy. I have to go to my office to work.
Really?
Good.
Ah! Don't worry about Kang Yoo Jung.
I made sure that she was okay.
Yoo Jung isn't that kind of woman you can play with.
Me?
No.
I'm taking care of her.
Besides,
Do I need your permission to decide how I treat her?
I thought you two had broken up.
Are you afraid that something would happen if I keep on seeing her?
Haterd can turn into love.
She's an interesting girl.
I won't listen to anything that has nothing to do with my work.
I seem to waste a lot of your time.
While I'm gone, you'll be busy workign for my hotel.
Thank you.
Let's start visiting branches in Seoul this afternoon.
With regards to the restaurant business, a guy from headquarters will help you.
Mr. Ahn, I told the security team to let you in.
Have you found the black box records?
I think I can use them when the prosecution wants some proof.
I have a meeting. Excuse me.
Sir, Ms. Shin wants to see you at her atelier at 2 o'clock.
Se Yeon.
Did you enjoy your date last night?
Yes.
Good.
I heard you introduced Ahn Do Hoon to manage the hotel.
He worked hard for the K Corporation, that's why the board approved of that.
I can't to such a thing on my own.
If you did it to make me angry, it worked.
Why did you want to see me?
Free meals for local children.
I hope your restaurant can help with it.
Sure.
Is that all?
You're trying to do good things. Then let's do it.
The K Hotel will fund the free lunch provided at correctional facilities.
Are you enjoying this?
What?
Giving away free stuff out of sympathy,
and trying to feel good about yourself.
What do you want to say?
You and I are both who we are thanks to our parents.
We're no better than them.
Can you deny that you're not using Ahn Do Hoon to get my attention?
Or are you really in love with him?
I don't care who you have a relationship with,
but not Ahn Do Hoon.
Min Hyuk!
Am I wrong?
I know you.
You never give up what you have in your grasp.
Get out!
There's one thing I want to tell you.
If you have somthing to tell me, come to see me. Don't make me come here.
It's true that Jo Min Hyuk's company owns the bakery building.
But he can't sell it because it's the company's property.
I can stop him.
Take it!
Do Hoon.
I said take it!
Pay part of what you owe Min Hyuk.
I'll take care of it.
Can you stop being foolish?
How do you think you can pay him?
I work here at night and have another job at daytime.
What kind of job?
I work in a western restaurant.
I can get a promotion if I work hard.
Did you know that Min Hyuk owns that restaurant?
What?
If you want to be fooled with him, then continue.
I didn't know.
Take this money.
I'm not giving it to you for your sake.
I give it to you for my sake.
And I'm begging you. Stay away from Min Hyuk.
He's torturing me because of you.
You said we should let each other be free.
Why are you doing this to me?
You make me feel guilty.
When will this end?
When?
Detective Choi?
This is Ahn Do Hoon.
Did you see that bastard?
Shit.
I hated him.
He was so ugly.
How can he be so ugly!
Yoo Jung!
- Hello. - Hello.
Ms. Kang Yoo Jung, it's been a while.
Someone reported you for a trademark law violation.
Mr. Ahn Do Hoon from the Legal Team.
Right. He copied some files last week.
What files?
The car records of the executives who worked with Pyeongchang Construction between April and July.
Anything else?
No.
Send those files to me.
Yes, sir.
Your father told me to escort you to the western restaurant.
Let's go.
How long will you keep the blakc box records?
For the executives, we keep them for 5 years.
5 years.
Wait!
- Hello, Mr. Ahn. - Hello, Mr. Ahn.
Why does Mr. Jo suddenly want the black box backup files?
He said he needed to check something.
Let's do it after dinner. I haven't had lunch, either.
Why do we need to backup black box video files?
All the files were deleted due to a system failure in the past.
I know you're a good worker,
but customers won't like it if police officers keep showing up.
Driver! Why aren't you working?
I'm not here to see you.
You didn't know that I owned this place?
I should've quit when I found out.
I'm sorry I didn't because I needed the money.
What are you talking about?
Take it.
It's a few months' worth.
Please stop torturing me.
Where did you get this money?
Does it matter?
Just take the money.
What I do to make money
shouldn't concern you.
Hey! Driver!
Please!
Please leave me alone.
Whatever it takes, I'll pay the rest of the debt.
She quit?
Well... She got fired.
A detective came.
The scary looking guy said Yoo Jung was involved in a hit-and-run...
An accident in the past.
The manager told Yoo Jung not to come back.
Ja Yeong.
What happened?
Why are you here so early?
Ja Yeong.
Someone reported us to the police.
How did they find out?
What a bad luck.
It's okay. If we pay a fine, we'll be okay.
Let's sell the rest of the stuff.
When the detectives showed up,
I was worried that if I get arrested again,
I won't be able to see my son for a few years.
Ja Yeong.
Do you want a Xanax? I just bought some.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
It's my fault.
It's my fault. I'm sorry.
The detective who showed up today is a friend of Ahn Do Hoon.
His name is Choi DoHyeong.
Aren't you going to answer it?
I guess the sound scared you.
What are you doing?
That's the quesiton I should ask you.
Do Hoon, what are you doing here?
It's glad to see you panic.
Tell me.
Why are you here?
It's about Congressman Shin and President Jo...
No more nosense! Tell me
why you're here.
Do you mind if I tell you?
The secret that you're keeping here.
You're trying to stop
the secret from being revealed.
What is it?
That secret.
I have no secret.
I don't know what you're looking for.
Find it if you can.
I will.
No matter how hard you try to protect your secret,
I'll reveal it myself.
Don't you feel regret
kicking Min Hyuk out?
If I was going to regret it,
I wouldn't have done it.
Why did you do that?
Min Hyuk,
he has everything,
so he always ignore me.
If you have Min Hyuk,
will you be happy?
Whatever it takes,
I want to have him.
I can help you,
if you want.
Everthing he has,
I'll take away from him.
Why do you want to destroy him so badly?
Has anything ever happened between you two?
You sent this to the board, right?
This is the same file that you were checking into
regarding our gallery's transactions.
Well...
I didn't tell Min Hyuk about this.
Does the world look different from the top?
I'm not sure.
But I want to find out,
how high I should go up for you to hold my hand.
I don't know.
Go as high as you can.
I'd destroy him
if I can't have him.
I'll introduce Mr. Ahn Do Hoon
from the legal team of K Corporation
to replace our former CEO Mr. Jo Min Hyuk
to manage the hotle.
Hello, I'm Ahn Do Hoon.
Yes, sir.
Yes. I have taken care of it.
Yes. Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Yes.
Where is my father?
He's checking his schedule for his upcoming trip to Germany next week.
He comes out again?
What are you doing here?
Nothing special.
I want to held a tasting event at the Limondleang western restaurant.
I want to ask his opinion.
It's good to see you working hard.
He'll be happy to see his heir working hard.
His heir?
He takes every good thing.
I got nothing even I'm his heir.
Just work hard.
The girl that you care about,
is she okay?
Driver! Driver!
How can you go to my house as you wish?
- Shit. - Where is Kang Yoo Jung?
You shouldn't break into my house like this.
Kang Yoo Jung!
Where is Yoo Jung?
Why are you asking me?
She ran away to get away from you.
Driver!
Let's have a talk!
Why are you asking me that?
After Kang Yoo Jung got out of my restaurant,
she gave me a large amount of money.
She called me the other day.
She seemed to be scared of you,
so I helped her.
That's all.
As you know,
I have nothing to do with her.
Then why do you act like you have somethign to do with her?
What do you mean?
You know better than me
what you are trying to hide.
I wonder
if you can hide that secret forever.
You look anxious,
I don't think you want to find her because of the accident.
Are you bored
since your toy's gone?
If you have nothing else to say,
please excuse me.
Hello. This is Ahn Do Hoon.
Sure.
Go ahead.
Kang Yoo Jung! Where are you now?
Find the bank that Yoo Jung transferred money today.
- Then search the area nearby. - Yes, sir.
Aren't you painting these days?
I don't feel like painting these days.
What did you and Min Hyuk talk about?
Is that why you wanted to see me?
He was looking for Kang Yoo Jung. I don't think he cared about you now.
He just didn't want someone else to have you.
Am I not good enough for you?
If I go higher,
will you give me a chance?
Due to denfendant Kang Yoo Jung's irresponsible act,
a young woman and
her unborn child were dead.
Therefore, we presecutor ask for a five-year sentence to defendant Kang Yoo Jung.
San, say thank you to the prosecutor.
What do you want to do?
- Bye. - Bye.
Driver.
What makes you scared and hide from me?
I'm not hiding.
I'm here to find a job.
I'm not scared and hide from you,
I just can't bear to see you anymore.
- Yoo Jung, are you done? - Yes. Have a good night.
- You, too. - I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye.
Don't smile. Don't smile in front of other people.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello. Good morning.
I'm hungry. Give me some food.
It's too early. Get out.
- I'll wait until it's ready. - What are you doing?
I'm hungry.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Enjoy your meal. - Over here. - Yes.
- One more bowl of rice. - Okay.
- Give me a bowl. - Yes.
Get out! Get out!
I said I'd pay you back. I'm working to pay you back.
Why are you harassing me like this?
Are you going to tell them that I'm a murderer?
Do you want them to kick me out?
Why are you doing this to me?
Do you think I'm that kind of person?
Okay. Anyway, come back with me.
Let me go! Let me go!
- Let's go back. - Let me go! Are you crazy?
Yes, I'm crazy. I'm crazy missing you. Stay with me.
Next on Secret Love.
Fire Ahn Do Hoon right away.
What are you doing?
As long as you stay with me, I won't fire him.
Mr. Jo wants you to work at his house today.
Did you touch other files in the Security Room?
Min Hyuk ordered the tech team to recover it.
Jo Min Hyuk is reinvestigating your case. Is that you?
Is this from your store?
Your father looked good.
Some guy took him.